2.5 Limitations of the project
   The limitations of this project are given below-
  ••• The reactor temperature was controlled manually in this experimental study
   with biomass heater by air blower. This was not a proper and accurate way to
   control the temperature of the reactor. Thus, the temperature fluctuation was
   high for a specific run which affected the result a lot.
 •:• The uniform heating of the reactor is a difficult rate.
   After every run the set-up was disassembled for feeding feed materials and for 
   cleaning of tarry residue of yield attached. It was reassembled again for the next 
   run and it was very difficult to make the system air tight in every joint.
 ••• There was no proper and suitable system for feeding and for char disposal. It 
  was disassembled for feeding and char disposal that was difficult and time 
  consuming.
  As there were no sufficient arrangement for actual determination of Activated 
  Carbon, so some visual observation are made but very little change happened 
  which can be minimize if proper lab and arrangement facility can attain in the
  determination of Activated Carbon.

